Michael Clavell

michaelclavell11@gmail.com michaelclavell.me

Game Developer

Needham High School

High School Diploma, 2016

Robotics Club — Treasurer

Marching Band — Drumline Captain

Summary

Current student at Rochester Institute of Technology studying for a B.S. in Game Design and Development while working toward developing fun and memorable gameplay experiences.

Skills

Fall 2012 —

Summer 2016

Programming	Software	Engines
- C# - Java - HTML 5 - CSS 3 - Lua	 - FL Studio, Reason, Logic Pro - Visual Studio, Sublime Text 3, Eclipse - Microsoft Office - Adobe Photoshop & After Effects 	- Monogame - Unity - GameMaker
Experience		
Spring 2016 — Summer 2016	Marketing Assistant, Coppola Properties, IncEdit website pages to show new and updated in -Manage data and mail lists using Microsoft Office-Scan and organize files on and off the computer	ce.
Spring 2015 — Spring 2016	Sales Clerk, Architrave -Set up and manage POS system, including solv inventory updated. -Work cash register and answer phone. -Stock shelves, teach co-workers, and clean the	
Summer 2014 — Spring 2015	Maintenance, Needham Golf Club -Clean golf house and restaurant facilities on we -Provide maintenance when needed.	eekend mornings.
Education		
Fall 2016 — Present	Rochester Institute of Technology Bachelors Degree in Game Design and Develop Expected Graduation: Summer 2020	ment. In progress